We'll start by looking at this data set.
我们首先看看这个数据集
It's a list of leads for Posh and Posy,
这是 Parch &amp; Posey
prospective customers whose business that they might try to win.
想要争取业务的潜在客户清单
Please keep in mind that this isn't anybody's real personal information.
需要注意的是 这些信息不涉及任何人的真实个人信息
This was randomly generated for the sake of this lesson.
这些信息是为本课程随机生成的
Our goal here is to clean up this data set,
我们的目标是清理这些数据集
to make it more useful for analysis.
使其更有助分析
For text fields, that means making clean groups that will be useful to aggregate across.
对 text 字段来说 这意味着创造干净的分组 这对之后的聚合有帮助
Let's start by pulling the area code out of the phone number.
我们先从电话号码中提取区号
Since the structure of a phone number in this data set is always the same,
由于该数据集中的电话号码的结构保持一致
we can use that to our advantage.
因此我们可以发挥自身优势来利用这一点
The area code is always the first three characters of a phone number.
区号通常是电话号码的前三个字符
We can get this using a left function.
我们可以使用 left 函数来获取
You can use left to pull certain number of characters from the left side of the string,
通过 left 函数可以从字符串左侧输出一定数量的字符
and present them as a separate string.
并将其作为单独的字符串呈现
If we just want the phone number,
如果我们只想得到电话号码
we can use right, which does the same thing but from the right side.
我们可以使用 right 函数从右边获取
Right works well in this case,
当前情况适用 right 函数
because we know that the number of characters will be
因为我们知道
consistent across the entire phone number field.
整个 phone_number 字段的字符数是一致的
If it wasn't consistent,
如果不一致
it's still possible to pull a string from the right side,
依然可以从右侧输出一个字符串
in a way that makes sense.
只要讲得通就行
The length function returns the length of the string.
length 函数返回字符串的长度
So, the length of the phone number will always return 12 in this dataset.
因此在这个数据集中 将返回的电话号码的长度为 12 个字符
Since we know that the first three characters will be the area code,
前三个字符是区号
and they'll be followed by a dash.
加上后面跟着的破折号
So, total of four characters.
共四个字符
We could represent the right function as a function of the length.
可以将 right 函数表示为 length 函数
As you can see, the results in the phone number alt field are the
可以看到 phone_number_alt 字段中的结果
same as the result in the phone number only field.
与 phone_number_only 字段中的结果相同
This is because, length of the phone number minus four
这是因为电话号码减去 4 个字符的长度
is going to resolve as twelve minus four or eight.
将被解析为 12 减 4 或 8
Which is the same as the phone number only call.
与 phone_number_only 字段的结果相同
When using functions within other functions,
在其它函数中使用函数时
it's important to remember that the innermost functions will be evaluated first,
请务必记住首先评估最内层的函数
followed by the functions that encapsulate
其次是外层函数